Yeah.
And just in terms of how we work together, because we use that for our own notes, action items, and we run everything through Claude of like what to do next. And we're very AI forward. I think this is going to be an exciting project if you haven't been on it. Circana is similar since you mentioned that.
But the project work here is intended to be very AI forward across the board, leveraging as much as we can as the tools of methodology and everything like that. So one of the stated purposes from Marty is to do as much of that as possible, get some lessons learning because they want this to be.
be an example project that we can learn from on how to best use AI technologies.
Yep, absolutely. I think that that's the way to go, record everything so that there's that constant context being built.
Yeah, which to that, so I've re-dropped these in the chat here. I've listed the scribble app repo, which that's the POC. We'll have to build some new repositories for the new apps that we'll be building, but we can reuse the meta scribble repo that's there. I've been ingesting all the meetings that we've had. So in fact, I even ingested the meeting from yesterday, the kickoff into there as well. So remember to use that.
that repo that has a built-in wiki, and as well, it's a project brain, so you can also query off of it. It has like our project roster, it has emails for the client in there, it has emails for us in there. So yeah, so I'm going to be basically like dumping everything into there so that, you know, everything will always be accessible via the team through that meta-scribble repo app.
Um...
Yeah. Additionally, I understood, which you, you know, you guys all watch the recording, but access to the Lucid board is on there. We're going to keep just a single board for the whole of this project. This way, then, if there's anything that we ever need to pull in from a different area from the workshops, we can always bring it over.
It also makes it so that, you know, all of us can, you know, communicate and work together, drop stickies. You know, you guys can come on here in the middle of my night and drop stuff on here during your day, and then I can, you know, review it in the morning. And so this will be just a great way we can all work together. So make sure if you don't have lucid access to request lucid access, because we'll be using this a lot for.
I'm getting things together.
I'm going to go ahead and just cover some of the new things that just came out today. So I will be updating the POC and I'm starting that work now. Eric sent me over some of the scribble new designs that they have, some of the mock-ups, as well as
Who was it?
Matt sent over also what some of their marketing is that they're using for this new Scribble app. Let me open that too, so I'll open up what that looks like too. I'll show that in a moment. On here, I've already started to go through some of this invite flow.
And I said, I'm going to update the POC so that then we'll have, you know, the exact start build out of what they wanted. We can also like kind of tune it and, you know, get them to be like, no, no, no, I wanted to do this, I wanted to do this. And so we can, you know, I can do the POC, you guys don't have to worry about that. And we can just use that to kind of help communicate with the client and make sure, you know, we flush things out there first.
as we're building this out. And just to kind of show this real quick, and we can go over some more things in a minute.
Yeah, so if you had a chance to go through and like play with the app that I, the POC that I built, here is now kind of their vision of it and their mock-ups. For them, mine was, you know, overcomplicated, but I mean, that was kind of the whole point. We wanted to throw, you know, the plate of spaghetti at the wall and, you know, see what stuck, see what they didn't like.
Some of it will become future features for later, and some of it will just be like, oh, hey, you know, let's see how they're using the app and see where they're going. Much of, you know, Scribble's persona and what they're trying to drive is, you know, this is about like human interaction and getting people to, you know, draw together, communicate together, like share things together.
Um, and so they they they really want to draw this like value out of um out of this application, and you know.
So I can share this as well. This is kind of like their bigger vision of things. Yeah, it's really little apps and nothing really big in there.
So going through some of the action items from yesterday. So this is kind of on my docket today, and I'll probably be sending this over to you, Pramod, as well, just so you can kind of review it if there's anything else that's kind of missing. But I'll be kicking off and starting to send out all of the invites for meetings. So like our daily stand-ups, syncs,
So I kind of had Claude kind of go through and start to build this out for me. As David mentioned, AI first, I'm extremely lazy and I can get AI to do everything for me, so I'm going to do that. If you don't have Claude connected to Office 365, it is just like chef's kiss to work with.
because it can plan your day for you, optimize your day, and even tell you like, you know, in 30 minutes you have a meeting, you probably should focus on that. I've had that actually pop up a couple of times where it told me to stop doing what I'm doing and focus on a meeting coming up. So definitely go to use that. Looks like we have.
Okay, what you don't have access to the repo?
Okay, yeah, yeah. So I made Pramod admin on everything. So if you don't have access through me, we can, I'll make sure that he's on there so that then at all times, you know, during your hours and your day, he can always get you added if I'm not available.
Um...
So, go ahead.
So you mentioned one quick question, sorry, on Claude, right? So obviously we saw the point about using Claude through Bedrock. Is that only for the API calls from the application, like a prompt and daily, any of that kind of intelligence or also for the...
Developers would know, OK, so Claude.
Yep, so right. So developers, right, you should be, first you should have requested the cloud access and then from there you'll just sign in and then that just goes to, I mean, we have like subscriptions on our enterprise and so that's what you'll be using to actually do the development. Additionally, I've been working with Ashu who is at some point next week going to bring me in.
and we're going to start using the ARC platform. They made a whole series of changes, and so we'll be trying to integrate that into our flow.
Karuna, you have a question? Go ahead.
If you don't have really quick, if you don't have cloud access, make sure you ask for the developer version of it, not just the regular version. You're going to be using a lot of tokens and spend on this project, so you need to make sure that you have the larger bucket.
Yap.
Questions?
Yeah, so Rob, I just wanted to like, since like...
I joined this call, started this discussion, so if you, if you don't mind, if we can just give a brief again what the current application and what is in terms of expectations on the requirements that will help to correlate the context or information that we are going to discuss further.
Yes. We are building a Scribble mobile app. This will be, we're going to be targeting the iOS first. I built a prototype which I actually used Expo. This actually builds a real app, so I actually have the Android version on my phone.
So this is a daily drawing app. So think of like Wordle and some of those other ones, they want this to just be like 3 to 5 minutes every morning. Like you just come in here and you want to do your daily drawing. You can share with your family. So like you can come in here, it tells you, you know, it gives you like a prompt of what you want to draw. You know, you can try and draw that for the day. You can, you know, do all the tools.
Mine's slightly fancier. Once you're done, you can then, you know, this is some yellow lines, just as an example.
You'll be able to record, because with this, they want you to kind of like tell a story on like, you know, why you're drawing this. And like my prompts are very generic. Their prompts are going to be, like they're going to generate a whole set of prompts and then, you know, target them like based on month and like events and holidays and try and make them like more specialized or even have like psychologists like reviewing them to make sure that, you know,
Mm.
this like really goes to like sharing and, you know, happy thoughts and, you know, working with people. So you can come here, you can, you know, say like, you know, oh, this is why I drew this, here's my story of why I drew it. You can save these recordings and later on when they go on there, you can actually then play it back so you can hear the person's recording of like, you know, their vision of their drawing for what they drew.
You can come and pick like, you know, what boards, so this is like who you're sharing that photo with. And so here I'm just sharing with my Forshier family. And like if my wife comes on here, like she can come and draw for the day. You can also share this out and have multiple people per day. You have like a wall board so you can see like, you know, past days of drawing. You can see like what was
Mmh.
what was said. You also can come in and kind of give emojis for it. Eventually, they also want to add comments back. I had added comments originally, but they didn't like that, but then a client or someone talked them back into it. So eventually, we'll probably add comments, but for right now, no comments. So there you can actually see the emojis stay behind.
Um...
As I said, you have them in the various different walls where then you can do other challenges. So like my son and I, my central little Zelda character. But yeah, so the whole point is just kind of like drawing, family sharing. You know, you have like your streaks kind of gamified as well. So I have kind of like a screen that looks like this. And then of course,
Of course, you'll be able to kind of like make an avatar, like adjust your names and stuff like that, and then kind of pick what walls and stuff you want to add or leave. And so, really, I mean, this is what we're building. It's very simple. Theirs is, as I said, mine is a lot more, has a lot more features, because I, you know, kind of built this from some of their original designs. Their newer one is going to be more simplistic.
So even like the drawing experience will be reduced down to like, you know, something like this where it's only, you know, four sizes and six colors. And so as I said, I'll be redoing the POC today to come closer to what they want here. But yeah, hopefully that gives you.
Right, so I have similar understanding about the app, but in general, like this app is already supported, I believe, on the mobile devices, right?
So I built this POC, but I vibe go to this POC. So we're actually rebuilding this POC from scratch, like a proper React Native targeting iOS first, but Android fast follow.
Mmh.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, I hope that answers your questions.
So, we, we...
And, by the way, are we sorry, please go back.
Yeah, go ahead.
Not everything, but are we already set for iOS development? Because once the things start, do we have all, you know, the provisioning profiles and all from their side? Because if you really want to run that fast, day one, everything should be ready.
Right. Right now, they do not have, and that was actually listed on the board. That is not the lucid board. This is the lucid board. So when we went through this section, as far as they know, they do not have Apple developer accounts. They do not have Google Play developer accounts. And so we will probably have to
Yeah.
Go ahead, David.
Oh, I didn't mean to interrupt you mid-sentence, but yeah, so some broader context. This is a very small startup. Their goal as a company is around mental health and enabling connection between families and
coworkers and others. So they're thinking about it not from a designing an app standpoint. They're thinking about it as a way to have connection.
work on mental health issues between family members, that type of thing. So their orientation is very different as a company, and they see this application as a way to form some of that connection. And they've done a lot of research around this with
the medical industry and they have some background in that approach. So the features and the things that they're discussing are really important to them. Like they're very passionate about it, but they also want to be super careful in the implementation. So they care a lot about the experience of the application going in there.
They care a lot about, we had a long discussion yesterday, for example, on the prompts. They want the prompts to the user of what you're going to draw to be highly curated and very carefully structured so that they're just not, they don't feel random, that they're trying to form connections between users, they don't have inappropriate content, that type of stuff. The first release is going to be.
be effectively a POC beta because they need to be able to move fast and see what can be done so that they can get more funding for this project. But the fast follow like MVP will be targeting minors and families and so take care A lot.
a lot about doing things right the first time. So I think that orientation is important. The other thing is their initial funding from AWS only provides them about 8 weeks of initial investment. And now they're going to seek investment from other companies, from individual donors, all of that kind of stuff. So we expect the project to continue.
But in terms of what we have to develop against is a very strategic backlog where we move fast through the initial core features and just get them as far as they can with the time that we have in eight weeks. They're targeting and have a relationship with AWS, so they want to be at reinvent.
That's their big target right now, to be able to show this at re:Invent and be ready and have a QR code where people can download it and play with it and they can tell their story. So that's the real goal that they're working on at the moment.
which hopefully we can be on stage for that.
Yeah.
Which I just kind of pointed this out, just they are like scribble.co and maybe at some point we can set up and do this. They currently have like a business to business version of this, where it's all just like web-based. Like David had set this up when we were kind of like originally talking to them, getting this all set and we kind of like played around with this. So maybe we'll have to set this up, but then you can kind of experience like their, you know, so they do actually have
Hey, Gaurav.
you know, existing product that they currently are selling, but we're building a completely separate, you know, mobile app version of this. And that's kind of what they're kind of like getting on to here now when they talk about this. But I cut somebody off, by all means, go ahead.
Yap.
So are we also going to build a backend for it or?
Yes, and that will be built on AWS. We already have the designs for that. Jonathan McCracken put those up, so we already have some initial designs for the AWS backend for this.
Also, because they're a startup, they don't really have anything set up yet. So we should assume to get started, we're using all of our own accounts for everything. And then we're going to have to help them set up those pieces. Like they're not set up on AWS yet. They don't use Teams or things like that. They use Google because they're just a small.
Company that type of thing.
A question on funding in terms of credits and because like you said, they don't, they're not set up on AWS, they don't seem to have those accounts, et cetera. Is as part of this project, obviously the one part of the funding is the fee for this execution. Is there a infra budget as well for them to?
whatever environments they are, is all of that going to be at R end.
So they don't have funding specifically for infrastructure. The funding they do have is from AWS. So AWS specifically just wants this hosted in their environment and probably through Bedrock. I mean, those decisions we can make along the way as we flush out the architecture.
But what they care about really is that just, it's an on AWS because AWS also wants to tell the story about working with them and what they're trying to achieve. So it's a partnership agreement. But they don't have a budget for AWS hosting or anything like that. Like we have to help them navigate.
More.
some of those pieces.
We'll also be using JIRA, so we'll need to set up a JIRA board as well.
Go ahead, Neelesh.
Yeah, so there are multiple queries which I have. We see there is already a back end application for them. So we say they are startups. So how is the back end application working up? Who designed that for the scribble app back end application?
Suren.
Are you talking the POC that I shared or the scribble.co like their actual application?
Scribble.com, exactly the scribble.com.
That.
I don't know, but I do know who developed it. So we can ask Marty those questions. He will actually know that. It was part of the team that built that was our previous company. And that's how we have a relationship with that because Marty knows them personally and is on there.
He just works directly with them. So we can ask some of those details from Marty and he should have some of that, or at least be able to point us to what they do have. They probably already have some AWS infrastructure, we just don't know yet.
So, anyhow, yeah, someone was about to ask a question. Pramod, you will want to ask that. Okay, so now let's talk. They have a backup which is already working, and we are going to utilize the same type of features on the mobile side, expecting what is there on the website. So, are we going to provide some extra features here?
What?
Continue, continue. We can continue.
Yap.
I don't.
I don't know that that's a fair assumption. I think this is a greenfield build. We should build it from scratch. I'll give you an example. I asked yesterday, one of the features that they want is observability and monitoring and dashboarding to know who's using what and some of those things. When we asked them about that, they said, yeah, there's a previous one built.
but basically, you know, provide us a new version of what you think is best. So they don't want us to be baggaged by what is existing. They want us to move fast and provide them a plan for what is better moving forward. And then maybe a future phase, those things, you know, come together and are.
are decoupled, but for now we should just assume this is its own application.
David, what I'm understanding here is they have come up with a fixed time estimate, but they haven't come up with the fixed features yet. So they are keep on grooming the requirement, setting up the features, but they come up with just a requirement that it has to be done in eight weeks.
I don't know that they have anything necessarily. I mean, there's a follow-up question with them on getting access to that stuff. What we heard from them yesterday is they're just expecting us to provide that guidance and help them get set up. So if they have something, they don't expect us to reuse that necessarily.
Okay, so the backend will be designed, deployment will be on AWS. They don't have an AWS account and no money to set up an AWS infrastructure that we are going to do for them initially.
I at.
I think we have to have a follow-up direct conversation with them about that. Like we should have a meeting discussion and ask about the infrastructure pieces.
We should have this at least one proper architecture design that what exactly we have to do, what initial details we are going to get, what user base we are looking here to support to this POC, and what is the turnaround time they are looking forward to. Because infrastructure is going to be updated based on the turnaround time, and
and the number of users they are looking forward for this application and the regions they want the support for. So that is going to impact the AWS costing and infrastructure A lot.
I think that's right.
And on the mobile and on mobile side, OK, they want to have an iOS application which is going to be using the app native. So just to understand, they are looking for an iPhone application, are they looking support on an iPad application too? About OS version they are targeting right now, minimum OS version, what devices they are targeting?
So that will also be required for an iPhone application. And yep, so that is a basic requirement which comes when we go for a mobile application development.
I think all those statements are right. Yeah, the one thing I would say there is they don't seem to know the answers to those and they're looking for our guidance. So for example, we should tell them, here's what I believe OS versions you should target for iPhone. Like they don't know those answers. They've never done mobile development before.
Because the framework.
For us, it's about making sure that it's in their hands and they can play with it and that they have a good initial launch because they want to create a test beta group and collect some initial feedback. So we shouldn't go too wide. We want to make sure that there's constraints so we can move fast, but also
You know, they want to have a successful test group.
They need guidance. Yeah.
Yeah, I think one thing, Neelesh, with all these questions, obviously there's a lot of open-ended things, but the way the SOW is is more of a time-boxed effort where we try to do the most value, highest value things. So I think as part of the shape phase, right, we'll obviously these questions are very relevant and we'll have to scope.
Dan.
Okay, we are going to be targeting this XYZ versions, these devices, etc. I think that's probably, we'll need to box down as much as possible and we clearly call those out.
And.
Right now, all the requirements are just pouring it into our box. So we based on the time which we have, we have to give them an application which should they should be able to test and the basic requirements which they have, those should be done at least. So that is something we also need to check that what we can accomplish in this duration.
So that the application, if someone gets it, yes, that's a scalable application. The required features and the advanced ones we can still look over to, but what can be done should be the required features, the most required features in the in this time frame.
Yeah, yeah, and I think that's where the in the Lucid board, where David and Rob in the call yesterday, they had bucketed all the green ones, which are like a bare minimum, the must have kind of, and then a low and basically a tiered set of high level features, but I think your point is taken just.
Rob and David, correct me if I'm wrong, the way I think obviously before the kickoff we were, they would have their PO, we would have a backlog to work with, but at this point it looks like with all the context we have, the initial story that they had given the POC that Rob.
build the feedback that we get, the designs, Figma designs, all of these will be the input and we will have to come up with a backlog and validate with them is what it looks like. Is that correct?
Yes.
So Pramod for POC as well will have the items in the backlog, right? Like the requirements, what we are going to achieve.
Correct me if I'm wrong, Rob, not a backlog in the real sense, not a backlog in a tracking system, but more of a story that was given to Rob, I believe.
Just a query here. From the QA perspective, I know I was not in the last part, it might have been asked before as well. So please pardon me if I'm asking. So the QA testing we are looking forward to is just a manual testing we are looking forward to or an automation testing as well on the mobile side.
I mean, we'll need the full test suite built in the application as well, but then there'll also be some manual testing as well.
OK, so, Rob, full test built into the application that comes up. OK, so there are three types of testing which we are normally talking about: one is the test case, which a manual test testing, which a QA does. Second is automation testing, which a QA writes their automation script, and they test it out running the application on a browser stack platform.
Third is writing the unit test cases inside the application only. Once the application starts, unit test cases runs. So what type of testing we are looking over here in these three parts, out of these three parts.
Well, I mean, we should always have unit testing for the backend applications. I mean, we'll be writing that as we're writing the application. But I also could see us having, you know, end-to-end test as well as those automation tests as well.
I don't think we are looking for an automation testing as well, unit test kissing as well.
We need to be, we need to scope it very well in that case, because if we are looking for unit test casing of an application, that do requires a good amount of time to write the unit test cases. I know we'll be using AI here, but still it will require some time to have all the cases taken care of. And I'm expecting we'll be looking for at least an 80% coverage here from the unit test cases.
Yeah, so I agree with that, but I want to be careful. We need to find a balance on this project for being able to move very fast for the demos for them. But also, they do not know how to manage these things. They're not going to have the ability to do a lot of that. They're going to need help.
and they have a plan to hire to bring people in. So having a good foundation is important for them as well. We just need to be careful not to spend too many cycles on building the foundation and architecture and test case base and not carry it forward because they have to move fast for some of their investment agreements and things like that. So we just have to find that careful balance.
on this project to make sure that we're not creating too much maintenance and overhead as we go.
So I have question like they have any existing automation framework in place that that we can utilize?
They don't have something. We have to make a recommendation and provide it for them.
Okay.
When Dave talked to us about testing, they don't generally understand, I think, the paradigms in software development. I mean, they're...
Mm.
They're smart people. I just mean that they're not engineers. When they talk about testing and those topics, they think about user testing and getting feedback from a community and understanding what people like and don't like, that type of stuff. So they specifically want.
user test groups and that type of more traditional feedback. So any test automation that we add is something that we are adding value for ourselves and for their long-term maintenance or some other party, right? If a different company comes in and continues this work.
work or something like that. We want to have a good foundation in place. But it's really what we believe is the responsible overhead for ourselves.
Then, then this one another question when it comes to the even manual testing as well, like using browser stack, like we kind of we have other simulators also in the market which we kind of use and then expected to test, or is it like we have to use real-time devices like iPhone?
like physically and then have the application tested over there. What is the expectation?
I think we can use whatever we want and provide a recommendation to them. The caveat there is they probably won't want to pay for subscriptions and fees to those things. But if they provide value and it's, you know, it makes sense, we can make a case to them to pay for something specifically.
Yeah.
So just to understand, what is the user base? Do we have any idea on this user base of this POC or this just going to be a limited user like 8 to 10 will be testing out and based on that the main project will be done?
So, so one do wants in POC language, the discussions that we've had is they get a full functioning product at every iteration that we can provide it, so the POC that Rob put together.
They see that as, we've talked a lot about it as a POC, but their expectation is like when we hand them a deliverable, that they can actually deploy that and use it and test it with a group. And we should think about it in that way. So every sprint, we're just building upon a real application. So it's a POC to us.
but they don't think of it that way. They think of it as a paired down MVP that continues to build. I'm just stating that nuance because I think it's important for us to think about in how we go about delivering those demos and handoffs as we go. So there'll be three of those in the eight weeks we have.
Maybe 4. So the first two weeks is really discovery. We don't necessarily need to have one of those at the end of that, but then the other three sprints after that need to have a real deliverable to it.
So, David, I see here that even, let's see, we built a POC what they are looking for as a product for them and gave it to them. Okay, it's good. But what is the future for us and that if we have given a POC to them, okay, we normally don't do such small applications for anyone.
But this basically happens that if we are looking for a bigger project to land on our company, so what if they just get this POC done and then go away? Okay, we are good, you give us a good product, we'll continue with this. What's the future for us, even if we deliver this in such a short timeline? It's a very short time.
for such an application. So what's the benefit for us for putting so much hard effort in?
There's going to be continued work on this. This is just the first phase. That's the first part of it. The second part of it, there's a couple of benefits for us. One is validating the new AI forward sort of working methodology that we're putting together that Rob's going to work with you on with the harness and how we work. That is an important story for Bounteous.
They have agreed to, they, the client, and internally, our senior leadership team has agreed to a press release story for this. So there is marketing benefit. There is also expectation that we pull this into methodology for how we leverage ARC and those type of things.
So we're going to be doing some experimenting and also pushing really hard on the AI techniques on this project with the intent of feeding that back to the rest of the company. So it's not just monetary of what are they paying us. It's also trying to evolve our business model as a company, which is an important benefit.
That makes sense.
Sure, David, so this client, Rajeev, trying to monetize through this application as well.
Yeah.
So, any monetization.
They do, they do want to.
They do want to monetize. They don't know what that looks like yet. That monetization is not an expectation of this phase. Like they're not going to collect money on the App Store release. We don't even know right now if we're pushing an App Store release at the end of this phase. We have to work through the logistics of that. With an iOS release, that's probably not a good expectation to have.
We've talked to them a lot about that, so they understand that. However, they do want to monetize. Yeah, they do want to monetize, and they want to make sure that we're putting them the infrastructure to allow them to do that.
Not even, not even.
Yeah.
That's what, what type of monetization are they looking for? Are they looking for the Google Ads to run in the app through which the monetization happens by itself, even if someone doesn't buy anything, any subscription or any model, anyone doesn't buy it up? And if they're looking forward from us to put up something like this, then we need to understand what functionality are going to be.
monetized here, subscription-based or one-time saving.
Right. So the answer is they don't have those answers and they don't have a philosophy yet. They need help to understand that.
Yeah, their initial thoughts were around, you know, maybe we can limit the number of walls that people could join. So that's where they can like join in their communities. Maybe it's, you know, if somebody pays and they get like 10 more colors. So, you know, they don't quite know that they didn't bring up the whole Google ads inside of the app. I don't know that they would want to do that. I feel like that would kind of break up their whole
like persona of being like a health org on that. Because I mean, if you get an ad, I'm sorry, that's going to ruin my health for the day.
I saw somebody go off comment. My God.
Yeah, I have a question. As David said, that probably IS release is not a...
May may not be an expectation for this lease, so how are we going to publish it for their internal users and all, because I've seen somewhere on the board that they since they have, you know, they have company provided iPhones and all, so they'll be probably testing on those and...
Use them for day-to-day review and all.
That's, we need to make a recommendation. So whether that's test flight or some other method, we need to come up with something to allow them to do that, especially because, you know, this is fully remote. We need to be able to create a process and they've never done this before. So whatever the latest guidance is, I think that we come up with as a team.
We should do that.
Okay.
So, they they are more iPhone company, so you know if we could do the test flight, that's probably like more sort of preference, but kind of as David said, like you know, we're leading this on their this adventure, so it's you know our best judgments.
So TestNet will still require an Apple account. Without an Apple account, it's not visible. And they need to have some internal and external tester. That's second limit.
Apple account is anyway needed for even for beds and all.
Exactly. And need to understand if they're going to test flight build, how many users, again, the question comes up, how many users they are looking forward to.
because we have a limit on adding internal and external users.
Okay.
So thankfully, we were getting all this in the transcript so we can, you know, take this for action items. As I said, I'll be scheduling a lot of those meetings and so we can get a lot of this stuff going, especially with our first two weeks being the discovery phase, we can hopefully start getting answers on these questions.
Yes, and we need to also plan since you know we want everything to be automated. We also need to plan some build machines which will require either Mac minis or something set up or all.
Build infrastructure and online.
Well, the team should be getting Macs, like actual Mac laptops to do the work on.
So are we expecting to publish the builds from laptops or?
I think probably we are expecting the complete CIZD flow and all.
Can we not build that into like a repository and then build that out and then have a stage location where we can store those images once we're done?
So, Max, we heard, ohh, so...
From the laptops.
Are we going to look for a device as well? Because testing will be done on the devices now. If we test on a simulator, they will be utilizing the Wi-Fi or the power of a computer, not exactly how a device works.
I think we should request devices. I'm new to Bounteous, so I don't know what the process is for that. And probably you're going to need to have those devices in NDO. So maybe let's get a request going for some test devices. I don't think you need a lot for this case for what we're working on right now, but certainly the team members who are doing
So.
work on that and testing it should have actual devices.
Yeah, I think we should be, we have done, we do that on other projects, so a couple of devices with the testers, the developers, we should be able to get those.
Yap.
And also, I have a question on the existing like application, how the current application looks like. So, like, can we deploy it somewhere to understand, do some hands-on on the application, like...
The web application.
Like if you want to play with the POC that I built, there's a link I shared at the top of meeting chat. You'll see POC link in the password below that. I have it hosted in Vercel. If you also want, I can also send you an APK for an Android phone as well. But yeah, just let me know.
I think Karuna's question was more around the scribble.co, but maybe playing around with the POC would probably be more useful. I think David and Rob said they set up something to play around with the B2B one, I believe, right? But not sure whether that would be very useful.
Okay.
Yap.
Ohh.
Sparr.
Yeah.
As mentioned, we could try and set up like a scribble.co sometime. And David, how did you go about doing the scribble.co when you did that, when we all?
Did you just do like a free account and then sign up and then just send us for that? We did that business business.
It's just a free account. Yeah, you can just go play with it. You have to add multiple people. It's designed to be like a work thing where you add, you know, multiple people. So when I created a free account to play with it myself, I added myself as a like a user with different emails four times to get it unlocked.
So, it's not the most...
It's not the most user-friendly if you're just trying to play with it yourself, but you can go in there and just enter, you know, whatever emails or whatever and play with it.
It's free. They'll give you like a 30-day free trial if you play with it.
Okay, that we see on the like scribble.co, there is a get free trial version that we should try.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, the sign up for free, yeah.
Wing it.
Okay, okay.
I would play with it just to get a good feel, but also I think a better understanding is the prototype Bob hosted on Vercel. I think that is a similar experience and closer to what we're looking for anyway.
Mm.
Yeah.
Okay.
I have one question which may not be relevant at this moment, but are we also going to support other touch devices like pencil or something for drawings, etc.?
Long, long-term, yes, but not in this phase, so...
Um...
The answer is that that's deferred.
We do know that they want Apple and Android, but that has been de-scoped because of the aggressive timeline that we have to work with.
But.
So if we see it from an eagle's eye, so let's see the QA part. Karuna, sorry, I'm asking the question on your behalf. So when do we think that the how the work will start for QA? Because initial one week if we are developing something, what will be the task QA will be doing? So Karuna, will you be able to write automation test cases if you don't have the build in your hand?
No, no, go ahead.
Or just seeing the UI screens which we have, will you be able to write that test cases, then the member test cases, and do the automation part?
Mm.
See, ideally, what I would expect is that, like, so we have screens, but like that may not be the right point to start, so we should have, first of all, as in documented the requirement that we are thinking about, put it in some Jira and somewhere, and then I first try to generate the test cases.
using that requirement and probably along with the screenshots that I can use Claude to generate the test cases. That will be my first starting point to start and see because screenshots or mock-up will always have, will not give the visibility of what actually we wanted to achieve. So we should have it documented and get it reviewed.
with Vermit. So then coming to the automation, like I see this is just a short week of time wherein we have to achieve a lot. So for POC, I don't think, but yeah, we can start on that, but I don't think I can commit anything at this point that we can do a delivery of something like that.
Karuna, my suggestion would be here is understand the timelines and be very realistic on what you can deliver in this duration so that that can be scoped out with the client rather than committing a major, major things that, yes, we do this, do this, do this, and we don't deliver out of 10 week commit and we...
Can be automated, yeah.
Correct, correct.
Good, good.
Right.
Correct, correct.
Yeah, Yap.
Give only three, so commit only what you've given is visible.
Good, good.
Yes, yes, yes. I completely agree.
Also, we could leverage them as test users as well and provide guidance and get their feedback.
So if we create a plan, they're very eager to play with it.
Yeah, that is like after we validate, like we can give it to them, right?
Correct, yeah.
Well, first we should do, yeah.
From the mobile perspective, by tomorrow morning, I'll try to spend some time to understand what is there on the load set, what has been done till now, what we are looking forward to. So I'll try to put some time there to understand the requirements and come up with more queries that what can be done.
Hey, Raman, David, one quick question. There was a reference to Mission Cloud POC and they talking about working with a single vendor. Just thought of any context on that. What was that? Was there a parallel?
Work that was being done.
So, Mission Cloud is...
is related to AWS and the partnership that they have with AWS. They put together an initial proposal, and I think even a POC previously, and were expected to do part of the application. So in the meeting, the reason that came up is we were asking, are they still in play? Are we working with them? Are we collaborating together? Are they
taking responsibility for some of this. So the answer is no on all of that. So they are not using them in any way, and the expectation is Bounteous is going to do 100% of the work moving forward based on the designs that they're working with and the POC that Rob has. So that was just a point of clarification from their previous relationship.
Why that's important is the original.
Basically, they created up with a six-pager proposal and initial going in position that we leveraged for the workshop that was written by that company. And so there were some of the things that were wrong in there, but they created the initial vision for the project. And so that's why we were clarified in that meeting. But
Basically, moving forward, they're not included.
Got it. Thanks. Thanks for that.
Yap.
Right, they had actually initially created like an AI pipeline that would take the picture, like render out the background, and then add like an AI background to it. They sent us all the, like a PDF of the research of how they did it. I recreated that and actually baked that into the Scribble app. After we used it a couple of times, Scribble didn't like, they didn't really like the AI background feature functionality, so I disabled it. But that actually does have the functionality.
Cook.
I even got it pretty well tuned to where like you could draw things like it's on a table and then it would AI put like an actual table with like a nice background and it would center it all right. But yeah, they just don't want that anymore, which honestly is great because then it just makes the app a lot easier. Because like we keep mentioning Bedrock, but the current moment, the only like AI that I was even using
was the speech to text. And that was pretty much it. And some cloud to generate some prompts, which even there on that point, since they'll be preceding the database with those prompts, right now our only AI usage will be pretty much that speech to text translation.
Space Rebstock.
Gogna.
As I said, I'm going to be sending out some meetings and start getting our scheduling and start getting some kickoffs. I can do 9 o'clock. It's 9 o'clock. So this is a 10 A.m. for me central time. So does an hour earlier work? And I was going to try and make that like our daily stand up at 9. I know David will be, you know,
touch and go on that one because that's probably a little too early for him. But does 9 work for like our internal, or actually these would be like our daily.
our daily stand-ups.
Do do you mean 9P.m. India?
I'm saying 9 A.m. Central Time. So does an hour early from when this meeting met, this meeting that we're in right now, an hour earlier, does that work for everybody? Because I'll send out that as our stand-up, which is my 9 A.m. Central Time.
What time did this meeting start for all of you?
Yeah, 730. That will be 730 PM IST.
So, 7:30, does does that work?
Yap, that works.
Pramod, I will have two overlaps on Tuesday, Wednesday for 730.
I'll let you know about that because I have some meetings going on every day around this time, but I'll let Pramod know about it.
Okay, maybe Rob, if you can add a couple of other slots, we can probably pick the best.
Okay.
Okay, what I'll do is I created a Claude page with all the meetings or emails that I need to send out today. So I'll send that to you and we can work through some times back and forth and then I'll get all that shipped out today.
But whatever it gets.
Sure, sure, yeah.
Cool, do that now.
So Pramod on the test cases management.
We go with.
Excel sheets or something or...
What is your suggestion? I, since it's all on our side, right?
Like Rob said, Jira, I think Jira test, this thing might be something we could use because Rob, you mentioned we'll be setting up a Jira, right, standing up a Jira instance or...
Yeah, I don't know if we have product management, but yeah, so we just need to set up a Jira and then I don't know who's going to be the product manager, but yeah, we can, we need to get the Jira set up.
P.
Yeah, we can have test cases also there, you're saying Pramod.
So, in that case, it...
The Jira does have, again, we'll have to see. So, Rob, would it, would this be on Bounteous? Is there a hosted Jira? Okay, yeah, not maybe.
Yeah, let's do this on ours.
Yap.
I don't know if can you create those for mine or would I need to reach out and get IT to do it?
Yeah, might be because we have not used Bounteous Jira for anything. So if you have a contact, maybe if you can initiate it, that would be good.
Oh, oh.
Or do you know if we can share a link to JIRA to the client and have them access because we did promise them visibility into the backlog. I don't know if those permissions have been set up for us in that way or not.
I think we can do that. We are using for the other project.
Yeah, it might depend on how our this Bounteous Jira is, because we have generally used Jira on cloud right for customers, the hosted one, the SaaS one, but if it's Bounteous Zone thing, whether it needs its publicly available.
We'll probably have to check that. Do you have, Rob, any links to any GIRAS from earlier projects you worked with internal bond?
I do, I do have some Jiras, because I actually have my own Jira board. I can put you, link you to it if you want, so you can try and test.
I think the issue is we don't, Rob and I don't have access to create new boards. We need somebody to generate a board for this project for us.
Right.
I can find out here who wants the, so if you can send me some links, right? I'll probably get to know where that is being owned and I'll try to see if we can create a board for us, create a project, et cetera, whatever is needed.
OK.
On our previous project, ***** set up boards for us and would, you know, send them off to us and he knows how to do that.
Right.
I do have a scribble board. I must have at some point had ***** create a scribble board. The link right here, if you click on it, David, that takes you to a board that's named Scribble. It has nothing on it right now, but it's a current board and we can use it. It's empty.
Yes.
Perfect.
Let's just use that one then. Yeah, that's perfect.
Yap.
Yeah, Yap.
Okay, I just posted the link in the chat.
I'll make sure to keep that in my notes updated that this can now be our JIRA board.
Yeah, this is perfect. Yeah.
Okay, so you see it, David. Pramod, do you see the school board?
Yeah, I was able to access.
But this is OK. This was something else, right? This was not the scribble board link that you paste pasted here.
What I just pasted in the chat is the scribble board link.
Yeah, I'm actually trying to add you right now, but it's not. I think I can actually just probably just use your e-mail. I'm hoping you're...
Just add an N, did.
Cook.
Okay, so hopefully you should have seen, you should get a request to be added. And then we can start adding more people.
I need to drop everybody. I look forward. I look forward to work with you all. Thank you so much.
Okay, yeah, no worries.
Thanks, David.
Thank you.
All right, so I just added you on there, so you should see it.
I did not get an invite. I did see two names listed there. Pramod Kumar. Can you just try? Do you see an e-mail ID there? Thanks. Pramod Kumar at Bounteous.
Ohh.
Yeah, I can try again.
Yeah, right here.
Okay, at some point, you should get it going through.
Yeah.
Sure, sure, we need to go back in.
And I made you an admin, so then if you need to add anyone else, by all means. Because basically, as I've already told you, I'm going to add you everywhere that I'm an admin, you're an admin. So then if I'm ever not available, then you can obviously add.
Yap.
Suren.
Yeah, on Bitbucket, somehow I was able to grant access to several of them. They were able to get in. Pankaj isn't going through. Is there a cap on the number of users or something of that sort? Can you try adding Pankaj while we are here?
I think for Bitbucket, there shouldn't be any limits.
I got.
Because that, I mean, that's the whole point. Like, I know we have seats on GitHub, which is why we're not using GitHub. Like, I'm on GitHub, but like not a whole lot of people are. All right, so, all right, well, I see there's two invitations pending.
Can you try canceling that and send it to the same ID?
OK, this one.
Huh, but Neelesh, did you get ohh Neelesh, I had to drop for a call, OK?
Edit drop, yeah.
See that cross, it's somehow it actually go through.
And it looks like...
Ohh, when you OK, yeah.
I mean, I could try again without the...
No, that is not... Wait, is that the... It's just not showing the last name.
No, that's not. No, no, that's not it's.
Okay.
One thing that might be it is they might just not have access to this Bitbucket repo side, because this is the Aegis Studio side, because I know there is also a different...
Bitbucket.
So we have a couple different versions that have basically this project name is different.
So I think they might just need to make sure that they're a part of HS Studio.
Nope, there we go. Karuna was able to access the...
I think the Jira board, yeah.
Yeah, Karuna was able to.
Yeah, data board I'm able to access.
So this is Pankaj ID. I just pasted the e-mail again. If you can just give it another try because he never got an invite apparently.
Um...
For Jira or the meta scribble app or what?
Yeah, this is, yeah, the just the scribble app on Bitbucket.
Okay.
Save.
Why is it showing that cross, the gray cross on the right?
That's just for exiting out the or clearing out the thing. So if you go like that, it just clears it. That's all that does. Yeah, yeah.
That's it. OK, OK, OK, that's clear all OK.
Yeah, so write, confirm.